# Nasser Bunduka

## Los Angeles CA

424.380.3895 nbunduka@msn.com

## **Senior Systems Administrator**

## **Profile**

Multi-certified System Network Administrator with education and experience in network & security management, offering in-depth work experience managing and maintaining server infrastructure and data centers operations, as well as configuring multiple Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows Servers, VMware cloud computing, EMC Network Storages, Cyber network Security applications, and CISCO network appliances in several unique business sectors including IT Service Providers, Financial Institutions, Retail Management, and Healthcare.

### **Education and Certifications**

West Los Angeles College Computer Science Information Technology Associate of Sciences Current Ecfirst Compliance & Cyber Security Cyber Security Architect Certificate, Cyber Security Architect, 2016 Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator MCSA 2004 YAT Education Institute Certificate of Achievement: Systems Engineer 2003 Computer Network and Security Management. Wireless Telecommunication Institute Computer Systems & Electronics 2001 St. Edwards Secondary High School 1991

## **Technical Skills**

Microsoft Hyper-V, Active Directory infrastructure, Active Directory Right Management svc, Active Directory Certificates, Adv. DNS, Adv. DHCP, Group Policy, File & Storage, AD.FS, High Availability, Printer Server, Disaster Recovery, Exchange email server, office 365, MS SQL Database, VMware Virtualization, Cloud computing, EMC SAN Storage, System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM), Windows Embedded, Routing protocol OSPF, RIPv2, EIGRP, BGP, IGP, IS-IS, Routed Protocols TCP/IP, AppleTalk, IPX/SPX, DOS Command, VB Scripting, PowerShell.

### **Experience**

# System Administrator Prime Healthcare Centinela, Los Angeles CA 07/2015 – 03/2017

Oversee Prime Healthcare, Centinela branch data center infrastructure by maintaining and managing complex integrated network, systems, and hardware. Maintained and managed Centinela EMC VNX Array and NetApp data storage, backup & tape rotation. Configuring and managing DNS, DHCP Scope, WSUS, user's accounts, user email accounts. Collaborating with vendors to support healthcare application Systems provided by vendor. Tier – III Support point of contact dealing with complex trouble shooting issues, & customer service support. Maintaining and managing VMware infrastructure, troubleshooting hardware failure, resources management and optimization. Managing, maintaining server upgrades, and vulnerabilities by patching, fixing bugs, and security related vulnerabilities. Configuring, managing and maintaining cisco router and switches within LAN/WAN.

## Systems/Network Administrator Bid Network Online. El Segundo CA

05/2014 - 12/2014

Managed and maintained server upgrades, and vulnerabilities by patching, fixing bugs, and security related vulnerabilities. Managed network connectivity between departments, systems and network infrastructure in the organization. Tier – I Support point of contact dealing with systems & network trouble shooting issues, & customer service support.

## Deputy Manager IT Service Rokel Commercial Bank, Freetown, Sierra Leone 04/2011 – 10/2013

Responsible for managing team involved in end of day banking transaction and checking figures for final merging. Managed and maintained server upgrades, and vulnerabilities by patching, fixing bugs, and security related vulnerabilities across its twelve branch offices. Documenting application procedures for IT staff orientation and managing their project plans. Managing and maintaining ATM systems and network infrastructure. Assisted IT Manager in Strategic Planning, executing of disaster recovery plan, Project planning. Tier – II Support point of contact dealing with systems & network trouble shooting issues, & customer service support.

### IT Consultant Linksoftech Integrated Solution. Kingston – Jamaica 08/2008 to 10/2010

Implemented and supported Microsoft Customer relationship management (CRM) and Point of Sale (POS) for retail management systems. Implemented, managed, and supported Server side infrastructure and application for small to large business sectors. Provide real-world solutions for home user by implementing WiFi, Internet TV streaming, Personal Cloud, Computer/internet service, and security camera.

#### Manager IT Service KPMG Jamaica 11/2006 – 12/2007

Responsible for managing team involved in providing LAN/WAN migration, application and end user support services to offices in Kingston and Montego Bay as well as to member firms in CARICOM. Implemented and ensured compliance with KPMG's information security program, including the areas of business continuity and disaster recovery. Resource provider for information systems audit staff providing security advisory services to clients. Tier – I Support point of contact dealing with systems & network trouble shooting issues, & customer service support. Managed and maintained server upgrades, and vulnerabilities by patching, fixing bugs, and security related vulnerabilities.

# System Engineer DCS Telcom SAE, Cairo, Egypt 2004 - 2006

Implemented and supported VoIP via Satellite using K-Band, KU-Band and C-Band; Installed, implemented and supported internet service via Satellite using K-Band, KU-Band and C-Band systems for client. Managed and maintained servers and computers upgrade/Patches for vulnerabilities. On site Position and installation Internet Via satellite 2 Way & 1 way system. Tier – I Support point of contact dealing with systems & network trouble shooting issues, & customer service support. Configured, managed and maintained Cisco router and switches within LAN/WAN for clients.

## System Administrator Worldwide Computer Service, Cairo, Egypt 1999 – 2003

Managed and maintained a small LAN environment including server upgrades, and vulnerabilities by patching, fixing bugs, and security related vulnerabilities; Assembling computers for home users. Assist in training clients how to use the internet and Microsoft windows operating system.